<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<configuration>
    <property>
        <name>PORT</name>
        <value>80</value>
        <description>HTTP PORT</description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>www_folder</name>
        <value>/var/www/html/</value>
        <description>Where to put the web files?</description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>servername</name>
        <value>hostname</value>
        <description>The name of the server. if blank or set to 'hostname', use the evaluated hostname (probably fqdn)</description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>admin_user</name>
        <value>twiki-admin</value>
        <description>
            Username of the twiki admin user.
        </description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>authentication_method</name>
        <value>HBAC</value>
        <description>Which method to use in twiki authentication?. Options are HBAC, LDAP or NONE.
        HBAC: Use PAM  (Pluggable Authentication Modules) for twiki to find users and authenticate them.
        	 This will automatically create accounts in twiki for users registered on the system, and so integrate with FreeIPA if you have it installed.
        	 You can control access using HBAC rules to the machine. If a user can login to the machine, they can reach the twiki.
       	LDAP: Use Active Directory provided by FreeIPA, in this case you will need a bind user and also the bind user password.
        	You can control the user access here based upon ldap groups
        NONE: Use default TWiki authentication based on user registration
        </description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>ldap_bind_password</name>
        <value>0</value>
    	<property-type>PASSWORD</property-type>
        <description>
            Password of the binding user. If using ldap this must also be set!
        </description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>ldap_group</name>
        <value>twiki</value>
        <description>
            Name of the ldap group where twiki will look for its users.
        </description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>ldap_bind_user</name>
        <value>kave_bind_user</value>
        <description>
            Username of any ldap binding.
        </description>
    </property>
    <property>
        <name>template_000_default</name>
        <value># Created automatically with Ambari
# All manual changes will be undone in the case of a server restart
# Edit the template through the Ambari interface instead
TraceEnable Off
Listen {{PORT}}
ServerName "{{servername}}"
DocumentRoot "{{www_folder}}"
        </value>
        <description>In order to ensure the settings we make are picked up, such as the port number, we create 0000_default.conf in the apache directory
        Advanced users will want to edit this manually.</description>
    </property>
</configuration>